mediabong.net 2018-12-27

# PRIVACY – Vuble

_[French version](http://vuble.tv/fr/privacy/)_

##### **  
PART I: VUBLE PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY**

**  “Privacy Policy” objective**

**The company, Mediabong** , doing business as **VUble,** and its subsidiaries, are committed to protecting your privacy and giving you control over the use of your data.

The VUble’s **Privacy and Cookie Policy** applies to VUble’s video content and advertising services (the “Platform” or the “Service”) using our own technologies or third parties solutions, operated through VUble company or any of its subsidiary or affiliate companies (“VUble” or “We”), **to visitors** **of our Customer’s websites** , applications, widgets, connected through the Internet and interacting with the Service. It describes our practices in terms of data collection, protection, use and disclosure.

This Privacy and Cookie Policy can be updated from time to time (see _Last update_ at the beginning if this document) without prior notice.

**Information we collect**

As well as many digital service providers, we may use technologies that collect anonymous statistical data on how the Service is used.

When we display our Service to end users through our Customers websites or applications, we may collect anonymous information that the visitor’s browser automatically sends to the server such as :

– the user IP address in order to estimate its approximate location (country / region / city) and display content and ads relevant to its location, as well as using our nearest servers to reduce latency to display our Service and improve user experience.

– eventually the “user agent” (ie, browser, type of device) and the presence of Flash plugin, for a suitable rendering adapted to the device or browser specificities;

– date and time of the request.

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information regarding the use of the Service, such as the url on which the Service was displayed, or the visitor’s interaction with the Service.

_3d party data:_  We may also use 3d party non-personally identifiable data regarding user interests or demographics (as an example, VUble occasionally uses Nieslen Exelate services to provide data and targeting information).  Besides, our Service may give access to 3d party contents or links (like a Facebook “like” button within a video for instance or a link to an advertisers website).These 3d parties collect the data by their own, following their own privacy policy, and although we pay a great attention in selecting the well-known and professional 3d party partners we work with, we can’t provide any guarantee regarding their privacy policy, security measures, or any responsibility for the way they collect or use these data.

**How we collect it: cookies and beacons**

VUble uses “ **cookies** ”. Cookies are small files containing text, placed on your device when you visit a website. “Session cookie” are suppressed once you close your browser. They are used to store anonymous data related to the content or ad delivery. “Persistent cookie” remains on the device for a more extended period of time, but only as long as necessary to fulfill our legitimate business need and as required by law. They are used to store anonymous data, either measured (for instance, the unique device has already seen this ad) or inferred (for instance, the kind of ads the unique device seems to like). 

Cookie technology is anonymous as it doesn’t identify a user personally, just a unique device. Note it can’t damage the system or files of the device.

“ **Beacons** ”, or also known as tracking pixel tags, are transparent images, iframes or javascript placed in a web page or in the Service. They typically help us to measure specific actions done on the page or within the Service, like clicking on a video advertising to visit the brand’s website, or interacting with the video. We may in some cases use 3d party providers for beacons placement or processing.

**How we use information**

We typically use data collected in two ways:

_Real time ad or content optimization_ : it allows us to manage the delivery of our Service (ie, display of content and ad), avoid displaying the same ad over and over, to select ad or content that are likely to interest you, to improve your experience (for instance, through geotargeting, choosing an ad in your language or dedicated to users of your country), to stop displaying an ad you choose to ignore or skip.

_Statistical Reporting_ : compiling these data as anonymous aggregated statistics, to show for instance how many unique devices have been exposed to the ad, how the advertising campaign performed, how many clicks on the ad, etc.

**What information we disclose**

Aggregate and non-personal information about our users may be disclosed for marketing, advertising research, or other purposes, to our Customers or third parties, and shall be used for no other purpose than those set by VUble and within respect of this Privacy and Cookie Policy. We don’t use the data collected through our Service for any commercial purpose unrelated to the Service.

We also may have to disclose information for legal compliance: for instance, comply with applicable law and regulation, court order, request for law enforcement, or as evidences in litigation we may be involved to protect our rights.

Non-personally identifiable data may be used, shared or transferred between VUble companies, subsidiaries or affiliates, for business or operational reasons.

**Security**

The data stored on our servers are only anonymous information (ie, non-personally identifiable). Once the data is stored, we use strict directions to try our best to prevent unauthorized access, such as firewalled servers, encryption, secured databases, and controlled and secured access rights for a very limited number of persons on these servers.

**Your choice: Opt out / cookie management**

As your choice matters to us, we adopted a cookie **opt out** process. It allows you to opt out from our advertising cookie database. It means we will no longer place information in a cookie on your computer or process the information associated to the cookie.

Follow the link here to proceed to opt out from our base and cookie drop: mediabong.com/optout. Please note that opt out will place a special cookie on your device to do ensure we don’t collect your data anymore. Please note that if you remove this cookie, you will also suppress our ability to keep you opt out.

You can also change your browser settings in order to be informed of cookie drop, decline the cookie drop or remove cookies placed on your device. Please refer to directions provided by your favorite browser in its Help or Support section. You can find below some useful information on popular browsers:

Google chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>

Mozilla FireFox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences .

Safari : [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=fr_FR&locale=fr_FR](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=fr_FR&locale=fr_FR)

Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/fr-fr/products/internet-explorer#ie=ie-11>

Please be advised that by choosing to block the Service cookies (or all cookies), some features of our Service may not be usable (or not as well), like tailoring the content or ad to your presumed interests, or stop displaying you a particular ad you’ve already seen.

**Compliance with market regulation**

VUble is an active member of **IAB** (Internet Advertising Bureau). Through this Privacy and Cookie Policy, VUble whishes to be compliant with the self regulatory principles of the digital advertising market regarding data management and privacy:  IAB Europe OBA (online behavioural Advertising) principles framework, although VUble has not yet asked to EDAA’s membership (<http://www.edaa.eu/european-principles/>) and Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA) in the USA.

For EU audience, VUble is also compliant with the latest European data regulation (GDPR).

**Request more info**

For any further questions or comments regarding VUble’s Privacy and Cookie Policy, you can contact us at the following address: privacy _arobase_ vuble.tv

For Europe: Mediabong – 34 rue de Clery, 75002 PARIS, France

For America: Mediabong Inc dba VUble– 122 west 27th street, 3d floor, 10001 NY, New York City

##### **PART II – VUBLE WEBSITE PRIVACY AND COOKIE POLICY**

**Website “Privacy Policy” objective**

**The company, Mediabong** , doing business as **VUble,** and its subsidiaries, are committed to protecting it’s visitors and customers privacy and giving them control over the use of their data.

The VUble’s **Website Privacy and Cookie Policy** applies to **Vuble corporate website** (located at URL [www.mediabong.net](http://www.mediabong.net/), [www.mediabong.com](http://www.mediabong.com/), [www.vuble.tv](http://www.vuble.tv/), www.vuble.fr) giving registered Customers access to Vuble Platform. It describes our practices in terms of data collection, protection, use and disclosure. This Website Privacy and Cookie Policy can be updated from time to time (see _Last update_ at the beginning if this document) without prior notice.

**What information we collect**

**Vuble corporate Website visitors** : As well as many digital service providers, we may use technologies that collect anonymous statistical data to measure the number of visits or unique visitors of our sites, such as Google Analytics, which may drop a cookie on your device. Please refer to Google Analytics privacy policy (<https://policies.google.com/privacy>) for more information.

**Registered or potential customers** : Vuble’s Customers or potential Customers may willingly give their contact information and related data, including PII (personally identifiable information), to Vuble by various means, including telephone, email, postal mail, the “Sign Up” button for Publishers, Producer or Brands on Vuble Platform, or other means. The submitted PII is used to provide the Vuble Service to the Customers or communicate with them and potential Customers. On Vuble Platform, the registered Customers can update or manage their PII. Otherwise, potential Customers can have their data updated, communicated, erased upon request at **privacy** arobase **vuble.tv**

**About cookies**

VUble uses “ **cookies** ”. Cookies are small files containing text, placed on your device when you visit a website. “Session cookie” are suppressed once you close your browser. They are used to store anonymous data related to your surf on vuble.tv website and Vuble platform in logged mode. “Persistent cookie” remains on the device for a more extended period of time, but only as long as necessary to fulfill our legitimate business need and as required by law. They are used to store anonymous data. 

Cookie technology is anonymous as it doesn’t identify a user personally, just a unique device. Note it can’t damage the system or files of the device.

**How we use/disclose information**

We **never share or sell your PII data** with any 3d party. Non-personally identifiable data may be used, shared or transferred between VUble companies, subsidiaries or affiliates, for business or operational reasons.

**Vuble corporate Website visitors** : we use the information we collect for anonymous marketing purpose, ie monitoring the audience of our website and the source of traffic.

**Registered customers** :  we use the information we collect for providing our Service as defined in our agreement, (such as giving you access to the platform or sending reporting by email) and sending information about our Service evolution.

**Potential customers** :  we use the information we collect for communication purpose.

**Manage your data**

**Vuble corporate Website visitors** :

You can choose to refuse that Vuble drops a cookie on your device (opt out) through our consent pop up on our corporate website.

You can change your browser settings in order to be informed of cookie drop, decline the cookie drop or remove cookies placed on your device. Please refer to directions provided by your favorite browser in its Help or Support section. You can find below some useful information on popular browsers:

Google chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>

Mozilla FireFox: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences .

Safari : [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=fr_FR&locale=fr_FR](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH19214?viewlocale=fr_FR&locale=fr_FR)

Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/fr-fr/products/internet-explorer#ie=ie-11>

Please be advised that by choosing to block the Service cookies (or all cookies), some features of our Service may not be usable (or not as well).

**Registered customers** :  you can manage your PII data once logged on VUble Patform and/or ask your account manager to do the requested changes. Please be advised that by choosing to block the Service cookies (or all cookies), some features of our Service may not be usable (or not as well).

**Potential customers** :  you can have access to your data and manage it by sending an email to privacy arobase vuble.tv.

**Request more info**

For any further questions or comments regarding VUble’s Privacy and Cookie Policy, you can contact us at the following address: privacy _arobase_ vuble.tv

For Europe: Mediabong – 34 rue de Clery, 75002 PARIS, France

For America: Mediabong Inc dba VUble– 122 west 27th street, 3d floor, 10001 NY, New York City
